iimk.ac.in 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting the IIM Kozhikode website operated by the Indian Institute of Management Kozhikode (IIMK). Visitors to our website ' **iimk.ac.in** ' are guaranteed privacy in their transactions. Information collected at ' **iimk.ac.in** ' is kept private and is never shared with other organizations unless mandated by law or statutory organizations. This privacy policy is to inform you about the types of information gathered and disseminated through the Website.

**Measuring Audiences**

Your IP (Internet Protocol) address is used to gather broad demographic information. IIMK logs IP addresses and browser types for security and systems administration purposes. These logs are analyzed constantly to improve the value of the materials available on this Website. Your IP address also helps us diagnose problems with our server and administer the Website. IP addresses do not provide us with any identifiable personal information. This means your session will be tracked, but you will remain anonymous to us.

**Cookies**

In order to better understand the way our websites are used by visitors; IIMK may use cookies, a small file that stores information on your hard disk drive. IIMK uses information derived from cookies strictly for tracking usage and developing site improvements.

**Outside Links**

This site contains links to sites outside ' **iimk.ac.in** ' IIMK is not responsible for the privacy practices, or the content, of such other Websites.

**Submitting Personal Information**

You can submit information to ' **iimk.ac.in** ' in several places on the Website either to register for the programmes or to provide feedback to us. Contact information from the registration or feedback forms is used to send responses or information requested by our customers. This information is used only for our replies.

**Site Security**

This site deploys available security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Children's Guidelines**

IIM Kozhikode does not knowingly collect identifiable personal information from children under age 13. A parent or guardian must initiate any requests for information from children under the age of 13 on their behalf. We encourage parents to supervise children when they browse the Internet.

**Privacy protection**

IIM Kozhikode does not utilize direct mail services or telemarketing so your information will never be used for solicitation.

**Hyperlinking Policy**

We do not object to you linking directly to the information that is hosted on our site and no prior permission is required for the same. However, we would like you to inform us about any links provided to our site so that you can be informed of any changes or updations therein. Also, we do not permit our pages to be loaded into frames on your site. Our website's pages must load into a newly opened browser window of the user.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you may contact the official functionaries of the institute whose contact details are provided at: https://iimk.ac.in/contactus.php.
